it's Christmas
[Music]
time happy happy merry Christmas happy
happy Merry Christmas to
you
you when it's cold outside in
down I hear Jingle Bells as the stars go
by I cookies and milk and
Candy present under the
tree it's Christmas
time it's Christmas time la la Jesus was
born to
usor of the
world it's Christmas time la la la la
it's Christmas time la la la Jesus was
born to
us it's
Christmas happy happy merry Christmas
happy happy Merry Christmas to
you to
you Mary and Joseph had a baby and came
from far to see sheers heard the angels
singing Glory to God for the newbor
king it's Christmas time la la la it's
Christmas time la la Jesus was born to
us savior of the
world it's Christmas time la la la it's
Christmas time la
Jesus was born to
us it's Christmas
time happy happy merry Christmas happy
happy Merry Christmas to
you to
you happy happy merry Christmas happy
happy Merry Christmas
you to you and you and
you